[
  {
    "question": "What\u0027s the name of Gons aunt?",
    "answers": [
      "Kite",
      "Mito",
      "Ging",
      "Kurapika"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
    "arc": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does Leorio want money?",
    "answers": [
      "To become a doctor",
      "To send it to e-girls",
      "So that others don\u0027t get it",
      "To buy large quantities of drugs"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "arc": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What was Gon\u0027s aim after Killua left him alone playing with the Chairman Netero?",
    "answers": [
      "Get the ball",
      "Make Netero use his right hand",
      "Make Netero use his left leg",
      "Let Netero drop the ball"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
    "arc": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What did Tonpa mix into the drink?",
    "answers": [
      "Sleeping pills",
      "Headache tabletsschla",
      "Laxative",
      "Rat poison"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "arc": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "How many doors are there at the Testing Gate of the Zoldyck Family?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "5",
      "12",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "arc": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Bisky\u0027s true form?",
    "answers": [
      "Boy",
      "Big Woman",
      "Little Girl"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
    "arc": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "How did Gon die on Greed Island?",
    "answers": [
      "He didn\u0027t die on Greed Island",
      "Hisoka killed him with a card to the neck",
      "He lost too muich blood when Genthru blew his arm of",
      "He killed himself after Killuas death"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "arc": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did Meruem die?",
    "answers": [
      "Volcano",
      "In the desert with Netero",
      "In the basement of the palace",
      "In the womb of the queen"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "arc": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Alluka?",
    "answers": [
      "Gon\u0027s sister",
      "A Zodiac",
      "The \u0027dark\u0027 side of Nanika",
      "Killua\u0027s sister"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "arc": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Genthrus ability called?",
    "answers": [
      "Nuke",
      "Massive Explosion",
      "Little Flower"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "arc": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is not a member of the Zoldyck familiy?",
    "answers": [
      "Milluki",
      "Killua",
      "Ollaki",
      "Illumi"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "arc": 1
  }
]